Good morning, good morning, good
早上好，早上好，
morning. Good morning.
早上好。 早上好。
You ready, piggy?
准备好了吗，小猪？
Jordan. How are you?
约旦。 你好吗？
I want to make I want to make a movie
我想拍一部
about you. Yes.
关于你的电影。 是的。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; See, it's really silly and totally
你看，这真的很傻，完全
unnecessary, but we drive our kids to
没必要，但我们每天都开车送孩子去
school every day in New York City.
纽约市上学。
Hey, Brandy.
嘿，布兰迪。
Are you sitting in the front? Yeah.
你坐在前面吗？ 是的。
Silly, because [music] it's probably
很傻，因为（听音乐）
faster if we took the subway, but
如果我们坐地铁可能更快，但是
every day before we leave the little
每天送
ones at school. It's just like us and
孩子们上学前，在车里听 10 分钟（听音乐）却有一种特别的感觉。 就像我们和
the children
孩子们在
connecting before we start [music] our
开始演奏音乐之前建立联系一样，
It's It's a special thing. It's an
这是一件特别的事情。 这是一种
indulgence. It's also really stupid, but
放纵。 这真的很愚蠢，但
we do it. We do it every day. Bye,
我们还是会这么做。 我们每天都这样做。 再见，
George.
乔治。
Bye, Brandy.
再见，布兰迪。
Bye, George.
再见，乔治。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; See you.
再见。
Every time I want to buy something
每次我想买
electronic or something, [music]
电子产品或者其他东西（比如音乐）的时候，
I always look for your videos cuz I know
我都会先看你的视频，因为我知道
you give the best reviews.
你的评测总是最好的。
Owning a car in New York City is
在纽约市拥有一辆车
especially stupid, particularly stupid,
尤其愚蠢，非常愚蠢，
unnecessarily stupid. One, because we
完全没有必要的愚蠢。 第一，因为我们
have the best public transportation
拥有世界上最好的公共交通系统
like at anywhere. And then two, because
。 其次，因为
there's nowhere to park your car in the
城里根本没地方停车
city. Which means you have to pay an
。 这意味着你必须支付一笔
ungodly sum to park in a parking garage.
巨款才能在停车场停车。
And then the parking garages are so
而且停车场
small that they have to stack the cars
太小，只能把车一个叠一个地停放
on top of one another. And when you want
。 当你想
your car, there are dudes that work in
取车的时候，车库里的一些工作人员就得像
that have to play car Tetris and move
玩汽车版俄罗斯方块一样，移动
other cars around to get your car
其他车辆才能把你的车弄出来
out.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; So, Jordan, who's one of the guys that
乔丹，就是帮
parks our car,
我们停车的那个人，
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; Jordan's from the Dominican Republic,
Jordan来自多米尼加共和国，
but on top of working here parking cars,
除了在这里做停车管理员之外，
Jordan has a side hustle.
Jordan还有一份副业。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 你用
&gt;&gt; That heavy duty lock is cuz you park it
这么结实的锁是因为你把车停
in the Bronx?
在布朗克斯区吗？
I park it in the street in the Bronx.
我把它停在布朗克斯区的街边。
So, this is a mobile car detailing.
这是移动式汽车美容服务。
You built this? Yes.
这是你建的？ 是的。   请
Tell me about the dream.
告诉我你的梦境。
&gt;&gt; Um I do a music, too. That's the dream?
嗯，我也做音乐。 这就是梦想吗？
&gt;&gt; Yes, I do a music. I rap it in Spanish.
是的，我从事音乐工作。 我用西班牙语说唱。   这
that's my future.
就是我的未来。
Have you ever seen his music? No. You
你听过他的音乐吗？ 不。你
know he makes music? No. What do you
知道他会做音乐吗？ 不。你说
mean you make music? Like you produce
你会做音乐是什么意思？ 就像你制作的那样
it? Yeah, and yeah.
？ 是啊，没错。
Wait, that's you? Yes, sir.
等等，那是你吗？ 是的，先生。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; You had no idea, right?
你完全不知道，对吧？
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
[music]
[音乐] 太棒了
&gt;&gt; That's really good, man.
，伙计。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; He works full-time parking cars.
他全职做停车管理员。
He's an entrepreneur. He's got the side
他是一位企业家。 他还有份
hustle. He details cars. He built that
副业。 他擅长汽车细节描述。 他把那辆
truck out.
卡车改装了。
And he's chasing the dream.
他正在追逐梦想。
The guy's a musician.
那家伙是个音乐家。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; It's the question I get asked more than
这是我被问到最多的问题
any other. Like look in the comments.
。 看看评论就知道了。
The question everybody asks like why
每个人都会问的问题是：为什么
live in New York City. And I don't fault
要住在纽约市？ 我不怪
people. It's a fair question. It stinks
别人。 这是一个很合理的问题。
here. There's crime here. The most
这里臭气熏天。 这里发生犯罪事件。
expensive taxes in the whole country.
全国最贵的税。
But like everybody here is on some sort
但就像这里的每个人一样，他们似乎都有某种
of mission. And if that's your thing,
使命要完成。 如果你喜欢那样，
it's not everybody's thing. If that's
那并不是每个人都喜欢。 如果
your thing, like it's my thing, you're
你喜欢那样，就像我喜欢那样，那么你
surrounded by people and it's their
身边的人也都喜欢那样
thing, too. And it becomes infectious.
。 而且它会传染。
And that is the New York City energy.
这就是纽约市的活力。
That's the thing that I thrive on. And
那是我最擅长的事情。 所以
that's why no matter where I go,
无论我去哪里，
I always return here.
最终都会回到这里。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I'm trying to live my dream.
我正在努力实现我的梦想。
Jordan, what's your mission? Why'd you
乔丹，你的任务是什么？ 你为什么
come to New York City? I came to New
来纽约市？ 我来
York to make movies. And I think like
纽约是为了拍电影。 我觉得就像
growing up in Texas,
在德克萨斯州长大一样，
New York was always like a movie city.
纽约一直就像一座电影之城。
Like this is where Home Alone happened.
这里就像是电影《小鬼当家》的发生地。
This is where Spider-Man happened. And
这里是蜘蛛侠故事的发生地。
so, if I want to make something,
所以，如果我想创作什么，
I got I had to come here.
我就必须来这里。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; What's your video? We're doing like a
你的视频是什么？ 我们正在做一件很
little cute thing of like all the people
可爱的小事，就像
in the park like in New York City being
纽约市公园里的所有人一样，都很
cute and all the Where are you from? Um
可爱，还有“你来自哪里？” 嗯，
I'm from Maui, Hawaii. Hawaii?
我来自夏威夷毛伊岛。 夏威夷？   是
&gt;&gt; Yeah, yeah, yeah. Why are you in New
啊，是啊，是啊。 你为什么在
York? I'm in
纽约？ 我来这里是
Um because I wanted to study art in a
因为我想在一个能给
place that gives me a lot of
我很多学习机会的地方学习艺术，并向
from people who really do it best.
真正在这方面最优秀的人学习。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你。 很高兴见到你。
&gt;&gt; Is he good? Does he Does he behave?
他厉害吗？ 他举止得体吗？
&gt;&gt; He's incredible.
他太棒了。   今天是
It's uh we're celebrating Star Wars Day
星球大战日，我们正在庆祝！
out here. Oh, May the 4th be with you?
愿原力与你同在？
Oh, yeah. You didn't uh you didn't know?
哦，是的。 你不知道吗？
Nice to meet you, Brandon. Nice to meet
很高兴认识你，布兰登。 很高兴见到
you. Good luck with the lightsaber duel.
你。 祝你光剑决斗好运。
No problem.
没问题。
Are those your pigeons or are those just
那些是你的鸽子还是
random pigeons?
随便什么鸽子？
How did you get your pigeon on her head?
你是怎么把鸽子放到她头上的？
I want 9:00 p.m. um I want I want
我想要晚上9点。 嗯，我想要，我想要
[music] 9:00 p.m. sunsets in New York. I
[音乐]晚上9点。 纽约的日落。 我
want to take it all in. I don't dream I
想把这一切都铭记于心。我不做梦，我
don't just dream any old dream.
不做任何普通的梦。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; super nice day and I thought it'd be fun
今天天气很好，我想去
to go to Washington Square Park to like
华盛顿广场公园
hang out and that place is just
逛逛，结果那里简直
absolute chaos. There's just a
乱成一团。
a pillow of smoke hanging over the whole
整个公园上空笼罩着一层烟雾，
and there's pigeons on people's heads.
鸽子停在人们的头上。
It is just That was madness, [laughter]
简直太疯狂了，[笑声]
man.
老兄。
That was not a relaxing afternoon date
那并不是一次
with Jordan in the park.
和乔丹在公园里轻松愉快的下午约会。
&gt;&gt; on her head. Godspeed, my brother.
在她头上。 一路走好，我的兄弟。
&gt;&gt; See you.
再见。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; This video is particularly um New York
这段视频的
City themed, so I thought I would end on
主题是纽约市，所以我想以一些
an informational note.
信息作为结尾。
If you're in New York and you find a
如果你在纽约，发现
small patch of grass like this, know
像这样的一小块草地，要知道
that it's most likely the the toilet for
它很可能是方圆
every dog within a five-block radius. I
五个街区内所有狗狗的厕所。
of it if you find a a a small patch of
即使你找到一小块
grass.
草地，我也不会在那里野餐。
We should just We don't have a lot of
我们应该……我们没有太多
options.
选择。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 今天天气
&gt;&gt; It's a super nice day and I thought it'd
真好，我想去
be fun to go to Washington Square Park
华盛顿广场公园
to like hang out and that place is just
逛逛，结果那里
absolute chaos. There's just a
简直乱成一团。
a pillow of smoke hanging over the whole
整个公园上空笼罩着一层烟雾，
and there's pigeons on people's heads.
鸽子停在人们的头上。   简直太
It is just That was madness, man.
疯狂了。
That was not a relaxing afternoon date
那并不是一次
with Jordan in the park.
和乔丹在公园里轻松愉快的下午约会。
&gt;&gt; on her head. Godspeed, my brother.
在她头上。 一路走好，我的兄弟。
&gt;&gt; See you.
再见。
This video is particularly um New York
这段视频的
City themed, so I thought I would end on
主题是纽约市，所以我想以一些
an informational note.
信息作为结尾。
If you're in New York and you find a
如果你在纽约，发现
small patch of grass like this, know
像这样的一小块草地，要知道
that it's most likely the the toilet for
它很可能是方圆
every dog within a five-block radius. I
五个街区内所有狗狗的厕所。
of it if you find a a a small patch of
即使你找到一小块
grass.
草地，我也不会在那里野餐。
We should just We don't have a lot of
我们应该……我们没有太多
options.
选择。